Lampson Nguyen – Software Engineer

Los Angeles, California - (805) 402 6754 • lampsonnguyen@yahoo.com

OBJECTIVE

I am a Jr. Software Developer whom is passionate about programming and a fast learner. I have experiences with web development, machine learning algorithm, data fusion and data science. With my career begin in Defense and Aerospace industry, I am experienced in Mission Planning software and process, and Electronic Warfare. I currently hold DoD Secret Clearance.

SKILLSET

C#	C++	Git
Java	SQL	Agile Methodology
Python	VHDL	HTML/CSS/JavaScript

TECHNICAL SKILLS

List various lab techniques you have learned through coursework or research. Consider whether this section is relevant to your career or academic goals.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Software Developer at NAWCWD - Point Mugu

August 2016 - Present

Work to support Navy's mission to advance its forces capabilities. Efforts include: supports of FMS in flight testing, and development of business data visualization software, mission planning, and data analysis.

RELEVANT PAST PROJECTS

Low Level Data Decoding and Data Fusion

November 2017 - Present

Developed a data driven software that process binary data into relational database, utilized SQL Server and Windows Services. Optimizing data processing functionality and data correlation.

Machine Learning Web App

July 2017 - November 2017

Deployed an image recognition web app that can distinguish different types of vehicle platforms and weapon types. Utilized technologies including Java Servlet for backend, python's TensorFlow library for deep learning trained model, and jQuery for interactive front-end look and feel.

Data Dashboard

August 2016 - February 2017

Designed and deployed static web pages to provide Navy's management the tools and data needed for their business.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Software Engineering